there are many organs in human body each organism key functions required for a body to work properly
the brain is protected by the skull the brain has many different parts each part is responsible for
different functions the brain sense messages to the rest of the body using the spinal cord to control these different functions
example breathing thinking hearing sites at such a heart is a muscle the pumps blood around
XNXX deoxygenated blood and pumps out oxygenated blood
lungs lungs take up a lot of space in a chest they allow it in hell and exhale in
breathing in fresh air filled with oxygen Dio
liver the liver carries how many important functions including cleaning the blood storing
in the form of a sugar code like agent and producing an important digestive liquid bio Kidneys
important job of filtering waste out of the blood this waste is combined with water to be released as
why are the bladder the body needs a least one kidney to survive stomach the stomach stores food you
mixers and breaks down the food into small pieces sir a can be transferred to the small intestine as a liquid
intenze the intestines are long coil cheats there is a small intestine and large
sweet leaving the stomach and choose the small intestine breaks down the feed mixer even more nutrients also
animated can't be digested travel to the large intestine the large intestine observes water
from the mixture and remove the solid waste products